Aswin Devanand

South Australia, Australia



aswin24595@gmail.com



451 732 080



linkedin.com/in/aswin-devanand-1a180a165

Summary

I have almost 3 years of experience in the IT industry Where I have developed my interpersonal skills and have been a great team player. I always like to work in a challenging environment. I am a certified personal trainer and volunteer myself during the weekends.

Experience



Credit Collections Analyst

Micro Focus

May 2019 - Oct 2019 (6 months)

I have been working for HP as a Credit and Collections Analyst. I was handling the credit assessment and collections part as well. Engaging with customers on their debts and analysing their financial statements to provide a right credit limit to improve our business.



Credit Collections Analyst

Accenture in India

Sep 2017 - Apr 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Working for International Clients, handling Credit assessment and collections part as well. Dealing with customers for the overdue payments, and analysing their financial statements to check the eligible credit limit.

Customer Service Representative

Sutherland

Jul 2016 - Sep 2017 (1 year 3 months)

I have been working for Amazon.in, I will be handling customers over the phone, chat, or email regarding their queries related to Returns and refunds, Credits and debits transactions, and products related queries as well.

Education



Macquarie University

Master's degree, Business Analytics

2020 - 2022

Pursued my Master's degree in Business Analytics and I have got Distinction Grade in the my final year project.



Anna University

BE - Bachelor of Engineering, Electrical, Electronic and Communications Engineering Technology/Technician

Skills

Leadership • Team Management • Microsoft Office • Financial Statements • Microsoft Excel • salesforce • SAP ERP • Management • Customer Service • Teamwork